<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator>
  
  
  <link href="https://enkrypton.github.io/main/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="https://enkrypton.github.io/main/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" />
  <updated>2021-04-29T22:14:15+00:00</updated>
  <id>https://enkrypton.github.io/main//</id>

  
    <title type="html">Enkrypton</title>
  

  
    <subtitle>Enkrypton's personal website</subtitle>
  

  
    <author>
        <name>Enkrypton</name>
      
      
    </author>
  

  
  
    <entry>
      
      <title type="html">Sound Voltex Keyboard Script v2</title>
      
      
      <link href="https://enkrypton.github.io/main/2020/09/15/SDVX-keyboard-script/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sound Voltex Keyboard Script v2" />
      
      <published>2020-09-15T00:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2020-09-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>https://enkrypton.github.io/main/2020/09/15/SDVX-keyboard-script</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://enkrypton.github.io/main/2020/09/15/SDVX-keyboard-script/">&lt;p&gt;Created sometime in 2017 to play Sound Voltex with a keyboard since I didn’t own a controller at that time. The code was then optimized, linted and documented by my freind Superoswald to create the final v2 script.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The script is fully doucmented with a quick setup guide all within the python file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are better Sound Voltex keyboard tools/scripts now in 2020. But this script serves as a memoriam to the earlier days enjoying of bemani games at home with my friend, Superoswald.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Download the script &lt;a href=&quot;https://enkrypton.github.io/assets/sdvx_kb2.py&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      
        <author>
            <name>Enkrypton</name>
          
          
        </author>
      

      
        <category term="project bemani" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">Created sometime in 2017 to play Sound Voltex with a keyboard since I didn’t own a controller at that time. The code was then optimized, linted and documented by my freind Superoswald to create the final v2 script. The script is fully doucmented with a quick setup guide all within the python file. There are better Sound Voltex keyboard tools/scripts now in 2020. But this script serves as a memoriam to the earlier days enjoying of bemani games at home with my friend, Superoswald. Download the script here.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
  
  
    <entry>
      
      <title type="html">GD Displayer+</title>
      
      
      <link href="https://enkrypton.github.io/main/2020/04/21/gd-displayer-plus/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="GD Displayer+" />
      
      <published>2020-04-21T00:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2020-04-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>https://enkrypton.github.io/main/2020/04/21/gd-displayer-plus</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://enkrypton.github.io/main/2020/04/21/gd-displayer-plus/">&lt;p&gt;Auto parse set information via the beatmap link and an API call. Link your guest difficulty and paste your api key to auto generate the BB code. No other input required!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full instructions are listed on the GD Displayer+ website which can be found on the landing page and by &lt;a href=&quot;https://enkrypton.github.io/gdplus.html&quot;&gt;clicking here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GD Displayer+ is free and &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Enkrypton/GD-DisplayerPlus&quot;&gt;open source&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      
        <author>
            <name>Enkrypton</name>
          
          
        </author>
      

      
        <category term="project osu" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">Auto parse set information via the beatmap link and an API call. Link your guest difficulty and paste your api key to auto generate the BB code. No other input required! Full instructions are listed on the GD Displayer+ website which can be found on the landing page and by clicking here GD Displayer+ is free and open source.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
  
</feed>
